<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-03-21T21:28:41+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/</id><title type="html">jmyrStudio</title><subtitle>Jekyll Template for Project Websites providing documentation and blog post pages.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to jmyrStudio</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/blog/2017/12/10/welcome-to-jmyrstudio/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to jmyrStudio" /><published>2017-12-10T13:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-12-10T13:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/blog/2017/12/10/welcome-to-jmyrstudio</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jmyrStudio/blog/2017/12/10/welcome-to-jmyrstudio/">&lt;p&gt;I am a Korean who is living in the Dist.7, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam and working as a freelance software developer.
I am able to join a project requires a full stack developer who is experienced in developing from desktop (based on Win32) to web (Front/Backend) and mobile (iOS/Android) applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have worked for several companies developing security products for Windows Server OS and mobile document solutions (like PDF) in Korea and made big contributions as a chief developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About a previous job, I was a chief software developer of oversea business department to set up joint venture company developing mobile services to apply the mobile document solutions in USA/China/Taiwan with a Venture Capital Bank in USA.
Also I have consulted and developed integration solutions between the products above and legacy system on a customer side for Top IT enterprise companies in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../../../../../portfolio/recent/&quot;&gt;Portfolio &amp;amp; Profile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kyung-dong-lee-45ba5a121/&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Kyung-Dong Lee</name></author><summary type="html">I am a Korean who is living in the Dist.7, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam and working as a freelance software developer. I am able to join a project requires a full stack developer who is experienced in developing from desktop (based on Win32) to web (Front/Backend) and mobile (iOS/Android) applications.</summary></entry></feed>